Undone.
lead-002
Undone until we set the monsters loose, oh my.
lead-003
La da da na na na na na na.
lead-004
Got the hang of every face you made.
lead-005
Have the knot before it's time to tie.
lead-006
Unpronounced announcement that you've come undone.
lead-007
Undone, undone, undone, undone.
lead-008
What kind of monster would you like to make now?
lead-009
That last one set the town on fire.
lead-010
Now make one that is twice as mean.
lead-011
And fifty feet or maybe higher.
lead-012
Undone until we set the monsters loose, oh my.
lead-013
Got a zoo here to keep the monsters in.
lead-014
So we can see them stomping around.
lead-015
Watch them try to eat the keeper whole.
lead-016
Zoo keeper keeps them all from breaking out.
lead-017
One, one, almost, just, just now, got out.
lead-018
Your eye roll tells me what, what your face can't say.
lead-019
You can't believe they even call that place a zoo.
lead-020
Choose your favorite monster beast.
lead-021
Suit the way you wanna be, be, be.
lead-022
Hunting Ed, head hunting Ted.
lead-023
Hide and seek's the game that monsters play.
lead-024
And play.
lead-025
lead-026
And play, baby.
lead-027
Five, four, three more to go.
lead-028
Now only two.
lead-029
The final fight between the meanest ones, I'll bet you.
lead-030
One has that kick, that kick that knock you down.
lead-031
Down, down, down, down.
lead-032
What kind of monster would you like to make now?
lead-033
That last one set the town on fire.
lead-034
Now make one that is twice as mean.
lead-035
And fifty feet or maybe higher.
lead-036
Ah na na na na na na na.
lead-037
Until we set the monsters loose.
lead-038
Oh my.
lead-039
They can shrink down to fit in any scene, just as mean.
lead-040
Grow up to be ten times or more.
lead-041
Change to smoke and drift through anything.
lead-042
Through the keyhole in the steel door.
lead-043
No way! Yes way!
lead-044
You're right, just right now, but you know I don't mind.
lead-045
Spend time watching monsters crash around.
lead-046
Got the hang of every face.
lead-047
You made.
lead-048
[Sustained sound; possible Undone]
lead-049
Choose your favorite monster beast.
lead-050
Suit the way you wanna be, be, be.
lead-051
Hunting Ed, head hunting Ted.
lead-052
Hide and seek's the game that monsters play.
lead-053
And play, and play, and play, and play.
lead-057
Undone.